Ah, Jay. I wanna court you.
اه، جاي. أريد أن أغازلك.
Kiko, the thing is…
كيكو، الشيء هو...
Everything alright?
هل كل شيء على ما يرام؟
Jay. I'll wait for your answer.
جاي. سأنتظر إجابتك.
We need to make sure that his plan doesn't succeed.
علينا أن نتأكد من أن خطته لن تنجح.
After two weeks of helping me out, my dad finally recovered.
بعد أسبوعين من مساعدتي، تعافى والدي أخيرًا.
Which means I can go back to school again.
وهذا يعني أنني أستطيع العودة إلى المدرسة مرة أخرى.
[Section E cheering]
[القسم هـ التشجيع]
Oh no. What happened to you?
أوه لا، ماذا حدث لك؟
Fuck Kiko!
لعنة على كيكو!
Jay, are you really letting Kiko court you?
جاي، هل تسمح حقًا لكيكو بمغازلتك؟
He's bragging it to all his friends.
إنه يتفاخر بذلك أمام جميع أصدقائه.
That you're gonna be his girlfriend.
أنك سوف تكونين صديقته.
We're not telling you anything, out of our concern for you.
نحن لا نقول لك شيئا، من حرصنا عليك.
I don't want any of you to get hurt because of me.
لا أريد أن يتعرض أي منكم للأذى بسببي.
What are you planning to do with Kiko? You're not even telling me!
ماذا تخططين للقيام به مع كيكو؟ أنت حتى لا تخبريني!
So you're concerned about Kiko?!
إذن أنت قلق بشأن كيكو؟!
So what, you're really not gonna tell me?
إذن ماذا في ذلك، أنت حقًا لن تخبرني؟
You're not allowed, Jay.
ليس مسموح لك، جاي.
Why can't you just take me with you?!
لماذا لا تأخذني معك؟
You can't be there.
لا يمكنك أن تكون هناك.
Is it because you're gonna fight? Even you, Ci-N?
هل هذا لأنك ستقاتل ؟ حتى أنت، سي-إن؟
Don't be so hard-headed.
لا تكن عنيدًا هكذا.
Ready for Round 2?
هل أنت مستعد للجولة الثانية؟
Keifer Watson and the gang. I have a surprise for all of you.
كايفر واتسون والعصابة. لدي مفاجأة لكم جميعًا.
[Jay struggling]
[جاي يكافح]
Jay!
جاي!
You're so hard-headed! You even followed us here!
أنت عنيد جدًا! حتى أنك تابعتنا هنا!
Jay!
جاي!
Am I dead?
هل انا ميت؟
I really jumped that high.
لقد قفزت حقا إلى هذا الارتفاع.
[muffled] Jay!
[مكتوم] جاي!
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
What if we didn't catch you?
ماذا لو لم نتمكن من القبض عليك؟
Ram's running away!
رام يهرب!
Chase them!
طاردهم!
- Let's go! - Run, quickly!
- دعنا نذهب! - أركض بسرعة!
You son of a bitch!
يا ابن العاهرة!
Man up, asshole!
كن رجلاً، أيها الأحمق!
Hey, get back here!
مهلا، عد إلى هنا!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Jay-jay, are you okay?
جاي جاي، هل أنت بخير؟
Let me get you water.
دعني أحضر لك الماء.
What she needs is space.
ما تحتاجه هو المساحة.
Can you please take this off?
هل يمكنك إزالة هذا من فضلك؟
Is your head hurt?
هل رأسك يؤلمك؟
- Damn it, we let Ram get away. - Are you really okay?
- اللعنة، لقد سمحنا لرام بالهروب. - هل أنت بخير حقًا؟
- Yeah, I'm fine. - You want some painkillers?
- نعم، أنا بخير. - هل تريد بعض المسكنات؟
This is nothing, really. Quit worrying about me.
هذا ليس شيئًا حقًا. توقف عن القلق بشأني.
Stubborn!
عنيد!
Here. Put it on your head.
هنا. ضعه على رأسك.
Tss.
تسس.
Got the nerve to jump, huh?
هل لديك الشجاعة للقفز، أليس كذلك؟
Jay-jay, are you okay?
جاي جاي، هل أنت بخير؟
Yeah. Thank you.
نعم، شكرا لك.
Jay.
جاي.
Don't ever do that again.
لا تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى أبدًا.
You made us all anxious.
لقد جعلتنا جميعا قلقين.
But what you did was so cool, Jay.
لكن ما فعلته كان رائعًا جدًا، جاي.
"I believe I can fly" was the vibe.
"أعتقد أنني أستطيع الطيران" كان الشعور السائد.
- [Ci-N laughing] - Asshole, will you quit messing around?
- [Ci-N تضحك] - أيها الأحمق، هل ستتوقف عن العبث؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I just wanted to escape Ram.
أردت فقط الهروب من رام.
Who is he anyway?
من هو على أية حال؟
He's the leader of another school gang.
إنه زعيم عصابة مدرسية أخرى.
We had fights before.
لقد تشاجرنا من قبل.
That's why he targeted you.
لهذا السبب استهدفك.
Because you can't listen.
لأنك لا تستطيع الاستماع.
You get dragged into other people's mess.
لقد تم جرّك إلى فوضى الآخرين.
I said I'm sorry.
قلت أنني آسف.
Wait...
انتظر...
It was your fault that I followed you there!
لقد كان خطؤك أنني اتبعتك إلى هناك!
Ah. Kiko…
اه. علامة...
Can I talk to you?
هل يمكنني التحدث معك؟
Just… the two of us.
فقط... نحن الاثنين.
Okay.
تمام.
Don't you have to go home?
ألا يجب عليك العودة إلى المنزل؟
No, I can stay for Jay.
لا، أستطيع البقاء من أجل جاي.
Yuri, let's buy chocolates.
يوري، دعنا نشتري الشوكولاتة.
You too, David. Let's go.
أنت أيضًا، ديفيد. دعنا نذهب.
You come too. Let's buy chocolates.
تعال أنت أيضًا، دعنا نشتري الشوكولاتة.
Come on. Chocolate. Yuri.
تعال. شوكولاتة. يوري.
Hey, Jay. What's up?
مرحبًا جاي، ما الأمر؟
Kiko...
كيكو...
Well, listen. If David said anything...
حسنًا، استمع. إذا قال ديفيد أي شيء...
Believe me... it's not what I meant.
صدقني... هذا ليس ما قصدته.
Kiko, I'll be straight to the point.
كيكو، سأذهب مباشرة إلى الموضوع.
I really don't want to have a boyfriend right now.
أنا حقا لا أريد أن يكون لي صديق في الوقت الراهن.
It's not that I don't like you.
ليس الأمر أنني لا أحبك.
I'm just not interested in anyone.
أنا لست مهتمة بأحد.
I hope you understand.
أتمنى أن تفهم.
I understand.
أفهم.
I'll still be here for you, Jay.
سأظل هنا من أجلك، جاي.
Thank you, Kiko.
شكرا لك كيكو.
I'm really sorry.
انا اسف حقا.
It's okay.
لا بأس .112
I should go.
ينبغي لي أن أذهب.
Bye, Jay.
وداعا جاي.
Chocolate's really delicious, right?
الشوكولاتة لذيذة حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
It's so good.
إنه جيد جدًا.
Hey. Where is he?
مهلا، أين هو؟
You rejected him?
رفضته؟
Mm-hmm.
مممم.
You're really something else.
أنت حقا شيء آخر.
You're amazing, Jay.
أنت مدهش، جاي.
Jay, go straight home.
جاي، اذهب مباشرة إلى المنزل.
Get some rest.
احصل على بعض الراحة.
So many things happened today.
لقد حدثت أشياء كثيرة اليوم.
Yeah, sure.
نعم بالتأكيد.
Oh!
أوه!
I'll do it. I can handle this.
سأفعل ذلك، أنا قادر على التعامل مع هذا الأمر.
Jay, I'll take you home.
جاي، سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
I insist.
أنا أصر.
[David coughs]
[ديفيد يسعل]
David, I know you have something to say. Just spill it.
ديفيد، أعلم أن لديك شيئًا لتقوله. فقط أخبرني.
Jay...
جاي...
I know you feel bad about what we did.
أعرف أنك تشعر بالسوء بسبب ما فعلناه.
And so?
و هكذا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
But you have to understand that we don't want you to get hurt.
ولكن عليك أن تفهم أننا لا نريد أن تتعرض للأذى.
I understand where you're coming from.
أنا أفهم من أين أتيت.
But I just hoped you told me the truth.
ولكنني كنت أتمنى فقط أن تخبرني الحقيقة.
And tell me what's going on because I was clueless the whole time.
وأخبرني ماذا يحدث لأنني كنت جاهلاً طوال الوقت.
You know our story.
أنت تعرف قصتنا.
What else do you want me to say?
ماذا تريد مني أن أقول بعد ذلك؟
Your rift with Kiko.
خلافك مع كيكو.
What's the reason for your fight?
ما هو سبب قتالك؟
I was the president then.
كنت رئيسا حينها.
Kiko and Mykel were the reason why Section E was banned from the canteen.
كان كيكو ومايكل السبب في حظر القسم E من المقصف.
One day, Kiko bullied Kit and Eren.
ذات يوم، قامت كيكو بتنمر كيت وإيرين.
Then...
ثم...
I told Kiko to face me.
طلبت من كيكو أن يواجهني.
And then?
وثم؟
He didn't play fair.
لم يلعب بشكل عادل.
He arrived with backup, and attacked me with a pipe.
لقد وصل مع الدعم، وهاجمني بأنبوب.
I can't remember what happened next.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر ما حدث بعد ذلك.
I just woke up in the hospital with Keifer.
لقد استيقظت للتو في المستشفى مع كايفر.
Is that why you don't want Kiko to court me?
هل هذا هو السبب الذي يجعلك لا تريد من كيكو أن يغازلني؟
We really don't trust him, Jay.
نحن لا نثق به حقًا، جاي.
So that's why your stricter than Angelo, huh?
لذا، هذا هو السبب في أنك أكثر صرامة من أنجيلو، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
For what?
لماذا؟
Because you're all concerned for me.
لأنكم جميعا قلقون علي.
That's nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
You're special to us, Jay.
أنت مميز بالنسبة لنا، جاي.
And yes, I'll admit to you.
ونعم سأعترف لك.
We planned on taking out Kiko if ever he pursued you.
لقد خططنا للتخلص من كيكو إذا طاردك.
I already turned him down. Don't you guys worry.
لقد رفضته بالفعل، لا تقلقوا.
But… what if someone else wants to court you?
ولكن ماذا لو أراد شخص آخر التقرب منك؟
Will you accept?
هل تقبل؟
David, you already have a girlfriend. Shame on you!
ديفيد، لديك صديقة بالفعل. عيب عليك!
It's not me.
إنه ليس أنا.
No one else's gonna court me. You must be kidding.
لن يتقدم لي أحد آخر، لا بد أنك تمزح.
- You're not sure. - Then who could it be?
- أنت لست متأكدًا. - إذن من يمكن أن يكون؟
Keifer.
كيفر.
Will you let him court you?
هل تسمحين له بمغازلتكِ؟
Really?
حقًا؟
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
He's not gonna court you. Why am I panicking?
إنه لن يغازلك، لماذا أنا في حالة ذعر؟
Why are you late?
لماذا تأخرت؟
What happened to your forehead?
ماذا حدث لجبهتك؟
Ah…
اه…
I bumped into a wall.
لقد اصطدمت بالحائط.
And we had a group project. That's why I was late.
وكان لدينا مشروع جماعي. ولهذا السبب تأخرت.
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء؟
Mom just left.
أمي غادرت للتو.
She went to Guam.
ذهبت إلى غوام.
There's been a problem with a business partner.
لقد حدثت مشكلة مع شريك تجاري.
Same goes for me. I won't be home for a while.
ينطبق الأمر نفسه عليّ، فلن أكون في المنزل لفترة من الوقت.
It's just gonna be you and Aries at home.
سوف تكون أنت وآريس فقط في المنزل.
Behave!
تصرف!
Yes, Angelo.
نعم أنجيلو.
By the way, your bike's fixed. You can use it now.
بالمناسبة، تم إصلاح دراجتك ويمكنك استخدامها الآن.
Thanks a lot, Angelo.
شكرا جزيلا أنجيلو.
Don't fight.
لا تقاتل.
Yes.
نعم.
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
Oh. Where is that?
أوه، أين هذا؟
Where is it?
أين هي؟
My bag's all messed up because of what happened.
حقيبتي كلها في حالة فوضى بسبب ما حدث.
Because it's just gonna be the two of us here, I will set some rules.
نظرًا لأنه سيكون هنا نحن الاثنين فقط، فسوف أضع بعض القواعد.
You can't leave without asking for permission.
لا يمكنك المغادرة دون طلب الإذن.
And you'll inform me about who you're hanging out with.
وسوف تخبرني من هو الشخص الذي تقضي وقتك معه.
And you're not allowed to...
ولا يسمح لك ب...
I...
أنا...
Jasper Jean Mariano.
جاسبر جان ماريانو.
That's not mine.
هذا ليس لي.
Who's the father?
من هو الأب؟
I'm not pregnant! It's not mine! Believe me!
أنا لست حاملاً! هذا ليس من شأني! صدقيني!
Is it Yuri or Keifer?
هل هو يوري أم كايفر؟
Pregnancy kit?
مجموعة الحمل؟
Why is it here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
And here's the thing...
وهنا الشيء...
Two red lines.
خطين احمرين
Positive.
إيجابي.
Denzel's pregnant?!
دينزل حامل؟!
Oh!
أوه!
Of course not, right.
بالطبع لا، صحيح.
This could only mean...
هذا لا يمكن أن يعني إلا...
Denzel got someone pregnant!
دينزل جعل شخصًا حاملًا!
Answer me, Jay!
أجبني يا جاي!
I told you it's not mine!
لقد قلت لك أنها ليست لي!
That's the answer of a pregnant girl who won't admit to it!
هذا هو جواب الفتاة الحامل التي لن تعترف بذلك!
[Jay-jay grunts in frustration]
[جاي جاي يتذمر من الإحباط]
But it's the truth!
ولكنها الحقيقة!
Who's that child's father?!
من هو والد هذا الطفل؟!
No one! Why won't you listen?!
لا أحد! لماذا لا تستمع؟!
If that pregnancy kit's not yours, then whose is it?
إذا لم تكن مجموعة الحمل هذه ملكك، فمن هي إذن؟
It's my classmate's!
إنه زميلي في الصف!
Jay-jay, you don't have a female classmate.
جاي جاي، ليس لديك زميلة أنثى في الفصل.
It's my classmate's, because he is the father.
إنه زميلي في الدراسة، لأنه الأب.
So, who's the father?!
إذن من هو الأب؟!
Is it Yuri or Keifer?!
هل هو يوري أم كايفر؟!
Ah, sir.
آه سيدي.
You made them come here?!
أنت جعلتهم يأتون إلى هنا؟!
Who's the father of the child?!
من هو والد الطفل؟!
Angelo, I'm not pregnant!
أنجيلو، أنا لست حامل!
Just admit it.
فقط اعترف بذلك.
That was fast.
كان ذلك سريعا.
We already made a baby?
هل أنجبنا طفلاً بالفعل؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Best day ever.
أفضل يوم على الإطلاق.
Asshole!
الأحمق!
Just bring me to the hospital and this will all be over!
فقط خذني إلى المستشفى وسوف ينتهي كل هذا!
Change your clothes!
غيّر ملابسك!
Don't bring shame upon HVIS!
لا تجلب العار على IF!
Go on!
إستمر!
You and you, you're going with us.
أنت وأنت، أنت ذاهب معنا.
You're gonna get married once you turn 18.
سوف تتزوج عندما تصل إلى سن 18 عامًا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm excited to see our baby.
أنا متحمس لرؤية طفلنا.
Asshole.
الأحمق.
Why won't they believe me?
لماذا لا يصدقونني؟
It even went this far!
لقد وصل الأمر إلى هذا الحد!
And this asshole probably have a nut loose or something.
وربما يكون هذا الأحمق لديه جوزة فضفاضة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
And this one has been quiet all this time. Didn't even back me up.
وقد ظل هذا الشخص صامتًا طوال هذا الوقت، ولم يؤيدني حتى.
I just want this to be over.
أريد فقط أن ينتهي هذا الأمر.
I'll talk to your dad tomorrow.
سأتحدث مع والدك غدا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Whenever you want.
متى ما أردت.
When did you become a couple?
متى أصبحتم زوجين؟
Is that a requirement?
هل هذا شرط؟
We just got carried away.
لقد انجرفنا للتو.
She was so good.
لقد كانت جيدة جدًا.
Ah! Mr. Fernandez.
اه! السيد فرنانديز.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I have the lab results for...
لدي نتائج المختبر ل...
Jasper Jean Mariano.
جاسبر جان ماريانو.
So, the test results came back negative.
لذا، جاءت نتائج الاختبار سلبية.
Which means, she's not pregnant.
وهذا يعني أنها ليست حاملاً.
Do you have any questions?
هل لديك أي أسئلة؟
I'm so sorry for making this urgent request.
أنا آسف جدًا لتقديم هذا الطلب العاجل.
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
If you need anything, I'll be outside.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء، سأكون بالخارج.
Thank you so much, Doc.
شكرا جزيلا لك يا دكتور.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
[Keifer laughing]
[كيفر يضحك]
Your faces!
وجوهكم!
I should've taken a video.
كان ينبغي لي أن ألتقط فيديو.
Oh my God. That was funny.
يا إلهي، كان ذلك مضحكًا.
You think this is funny?
هل تعتقد أن هذا مضحك؟
Yeah. It's pretty funny.
نعم، إنه مضحك جدًا.
You need help.
انت بحاجة الى مساعدة.
Okay.
تمام.
Gotcha.
فهمتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[Keifer laughing]
[كيفر يضحك]
Jay.
جاي.
Jay!
جاي!
I'll apologize in behalf of Keifer.
سأعتذر نيابة عن كايفر.
I don't need your apology.
لا أحتاج إلى اعتذارك.
Keifer's horrible. But his enablers are just as bad as him!
كايفر فظيع. لكن من مكنوه من ذلك لا يقل عنه سوءًا!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Not for Keifer, but for me.
ليس من أجل كايفر، بل من أجلي.
I'm sorry because I let it happen, Jay.
أنا آسف لأنني سمحت لهذا أن يحدث، جاي.
[Keifer chuckling]
[كيفر يضحك]
Tss.
ت.س.
[Jay-jay punches Keifer]
[جاي جاي يضرب كايفر]
Jay-jay...
جاي جاي...
Keifer really did that?
هل فعل كايفر ذلك حقا؟
Hmm.
همم.
But where did you get that pregnancy test, Jay?
ولكن من أين حصلت على اختبار الحمل هذا يا جاي؟
I saw it outside.
رأيته بالخارج.
I got curious, so I picked it up.
لقد أصبحت فضوليًا، لذلك التقطته.
You really enjoy picking up other people's trash, don't you?
أنت تستمتع حقًا بجمع قمامة الآخرين، أليس كذلك؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
If I hadn't kept Mica's letter, you'd still be heartbroken now.
لو لم أحتفظ برسالة ميكا، لكان قلبك لا يزال مكسورًا الآن.
Tss.
تسس.
You're just a meddler.
أنت مجرد متطفل.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Huh? Did you guys hear something?
هاه؟ هل سمعتم شيئا؟
He said you're a meddler.
قال أنك متدخل.
Oh! Nothing.
اوه! لا شيء.
Who said that?
من قال ذلك؟
Childish.
طفولي.
Asshole!
الأحمق!
It was a prank!
لقد كانت مزحة!
On my family?!
على عائلتي؟!
Well, it wasn't funny.
حسنًا، لم يكن الأمر مضحكًا.
Guys.
شباب.
They said we need five representatives for the assembly later.
قالوا إننا بحاجة إلى خمسة ممثلين للجمعية لاحقًا.
Yuri,
يوري
Rory,
روري
Edrix...
إدريكس...
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Fuck yeah!
نعم اللعنة!
And Jay-Jay.
وجاي جاي.
Come with us.
تعال معنا.
Me? To the assembly?
أنا؟ إلى الجمعية؟
Yeah. Come on.
نعم، هيا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
He's mad at me, but he wants me at the assembly?
إنه غاضب مني، لكنه يريدني في الجمعية؟
He's nuts.
إنه مجنون.
Take care, take care.
اعتني بنفسك، اعتني بنفسك.
You belong in Section E, right?
أنت تنتمي إلى القسم E، أليس كذلك؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Edrix.
إدريكس.
What's going on with the King of Assholes?
ماذا يحدث مع ملك الحمقى؟
Maybe he's trying to apologize?
ربما يحاول الإعتذار؟
Whatever! I'm still mad at him!
مهما يكن! مازلت غاضبة منه!
Hi, Jay.
مرحباً، جاي.
Eyes in front.
عيون في الأمام.
Is everyone here for the assembly?
هل الجميع هنا للتجمع؟
Okay.
تمام.
Then, let's begin.
إذن فلنبدأ.
Section A.
القسم أ.
Section A representative.
ممثل القسم أ.
Freya Hidalgo.
فريا هيدالغو.
Student Report: Zero suspensions, no violations.
تقرير الطالب: لا يوجد إيقافات ولا مخالفات.
Homeroom Report: Airconditioning unit, needs replacement.
تقرير الفصل الدراسي: وحدة تكييف الهواء تحتاج إلى الاستبدال.
And suggestions: a brand-new room for Section A.
وإقتراحات: غرفة جديدة تماما للقسم أ.
Ain't that right?
أليس هذا صحيحا؟
Section B?
القسم ب؟
Section B representative.
ممثل القسم ب.
I'm Ashley Santarina.
أنا اشلي سانتارينا.
No suspensions, two violations. And for suggestions:
لا يوجد إيقاف، مخالفتان. وللحصول على اقتراحات:
Deeper of our comfort.
أعمق من راحتنا.
Section C?
القسم ج؟
Section C representative, Rakki San Diego, myself.
ممثل القسم C، راكي سان دييغو، وأنا.
Student report: One suspension, no violations.
تقرير الطالب: إيقاف واحد، ولا مخالفات.
Homeroom Report: Our ceiling fan needs repair.
تقرير الفصل الدراسي: مروحة السقف لدينا بحاجة إلى الإصلاح.
As for the suggestions, right now we have none.
أما بالنسبة للاقتراحات، فليس لدينا أي اقتراح في الوقت الراهن.
Section D.
القسم د.
Section D representative...
ممثل القسم د...
Yuri, what does the school do with the homeroom report and suggestions?
يوري، ماذا تفعل المدرسة بتقرير الفصل الدراسي والاقتراحات؟
They prioritize the homeroom report.
إنهم يعطون الأولوية لتقرير الفصل الدراسي.
They ignore the suggestions most of the time.
إنهم يتجاهلون الاقتراحات في معظم الأوقات.
Section E representative, Mark Keifer Watson.
ممثل القسم E، مارك كايفر واتسون.
Four suspensions, two violations.
أربع إيقافات ومخالفتين.
Homeroom report: None.
تقرير الفصل الدراسي: لا يوجد.
Suggestions: None.
الاقتراحات: لا يوجد.
Hey.
يا.
What?
ماذا؟
Why didn't you mention the girl's restroom of our building?
لماذا لم تذكري حمام الفتيات في مبنانا؟
They don't care about us.
إنهم لا يهتمون بنا.
Next topic, festival.
الموضوع التالي، المهرجان.
[students react excitedly]
[يتفاعل الطلاب بحماس]
Let's divide the assignments.
دعونا نقسم المهام.
Section A.
القسم أ.
Program organizers.
منظمي البرنامج.
Section B.
القسم ب.
Sports fest!
مهرجان رياضي!
Section C.
القسم ج.
Booths and snacks, we'll do it.
أكشاك ووجبات خفيفة، سنفعل ذلك.
Section D?
القسم د؟
Security.
حماية.
Section E.
القسم هـ.
Garbage collector and night security.
جامع القمامة والأمن الليلي.
Yes!
نعم!
Oh my gosh!
يا إلهي!
Garbage collector? Just where they belong.
جامع القمامة؟ حيث ينتمي بالضبط.
Happy now?
هل أنت سعيد الآن؟
I have an announcement, We made some changes.
لدي إعلان، لقد أجرينا بعض التغييرات.
We are not gonna push through with the King and Queen of HVIS.
نحن لن نستمر مع الملك والملكة في HVIS.
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
But, listen up.
ولكن استمع.
We're gonna have a pageant for Mr. Pretty and Ms. Handsome.
سوف نقيم مسابقة لاختيار السيد الجميل والسيدة الوسيمة.
Girls will dress up as boys and the boys will dress up as girls.
سترتدي الفتيات ملابس الأولاد وسيرتدي الأولاد ملابس الفتيات.
Each section should have a representative.
ينبغي أن يكون لكل قسم ممثل.
One girl and one boy.
فتاة واحدة وولد واحد.
Wait, I'm the only girl in our class.
انتظري، أنا الفتاة الوحيدة في صفنا.
- I don't want to join. - We're not participating in that.
- لا أريد الانضمام. - نحن لا نشارك في ذلك.
Why?
لماذا؟
- They're not gonna include us. - Oh.
- لن يشملونا. - أوه.
- Ma'am. I have a suggestion. - Yes, Ms. Hidalgo?
- سيدتي، لدي اقتراح. - نعم، سيدة هيدالغو؟
What if we let Section E join this year?
ماذا لو سمحنا للقسم E بالانضمام هذا العام؟
All... events.
جميع... الأحداث.
Well...
حسنًا...
We'll think about that.
سوف نفكر في هذا.
So excited.
أنا متحمس جدًا.
Damn you, Freya! I don't want to join Ms. Pogi.
لعنة عليك يا فريا! لا أريد الانضمام إلى السيدة بوجي.
[Section E clammoring]
[القسم هـ الصخب]
- Stop pushing! - Shut up. I was first.
- توقف عن الدفع! - اسكت. لقد كنت الأول.
Hey, hey, hey!
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا!
You're all lining up, huh? Did you all pay your shares?
أنتم جميعًا تقفون في طابور، أليس كذلك؟ هل دفعتم جميعًا أسهمكم؟
Hey. You're gonna ask us to pay?
مهلا، هل ستطلب منا الدفع؟
I will ask you to pay up if you don't line up properly.
سأطلب منك الدفع إذا لم تصطف بشكل صحيح.
[Keifer clears his throat]
[كيفر يصفي حلقه]
- Yeah, you're gonna get yours too. - Hurry up.
- نعم، سوف تحصل على خاصتك أيضًا. - أسرع.
[Section E chattering]
[القسم هـ الثرثرة]
- Can you hurry up? - That's good, I'm on a diet.
- هل يمكنك الإسراع؟ - هذا جيد، أنا على حمية غذائية.
Diet?
نظام عذائي؟
Your mom.
أمك .456
Give me a spoonful.
أعطني ملعقة.
How special is he?
ما مدى خصوصيته؟
Jay-jay personally brings his food to him.
جاي جاي يحضر له طعامه شخصيًا.
- I'm just paying what I owe. - Really now.
- أنا فقط أدفع ما عليّ. - حقا الآن.
[Section E boys chattering]
[القسم E الأولاد يتحدثون]
- Do you think I'm poor? - Just eat already.
- هل تظن أنني فقير؟ - فقط كلي.
I'm hungry!
أنا جائع!
- Give me that! - Hey!
- أعطني هذا! - مهلا!
Denzel. Eat up.
دنزل، تناول الطعام.
So it's not just you who's special, Keifer.
لذا، ليس أنت فقط من هو مميز، كايفر.
Just shut up and eat.
فقط اسكت وكل.
Thank you, Jay, but…
شكرا لك جاي، ولكن...
I don't have an appetite.
ليس لدي شهية.
Do you have a problem?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
It's okay to share with me. You know that, right?
لا بأس من مشاركتي، أنت تعلم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
It's nothing. I just don't want to eat.
لا شيء، أنا فقط لا أريد أن آكل.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Denzel, it's obvious something's bugging you. Just let it out.
دينزل، من الواضح أن هناك شيئًا يزعجك. فقط دع الأمر يختفي.
Is this about a girl?
هل هذا يتعلق بفتاة؟
Are you broken-hearted?
هل أنت منكسر القلب؟
Were you rejected?
هل تم رفضك؟
Did you get someone pregnant?
هل تسببت في حمل شخص ما؟
[Denzel clears throat]
[دينزل يصفي حلقه]
Jay...
جاي...
I have something to confess.
عندي شيء لأعترف به.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Go on, continue. Quickly.
إستمر، إستمر، بسرعة.
I'm pregnant.
انا حامل.
Huh?!
هاه؟!
I'm just pretending to be a man because I'm terrified of them.
أنا فقط أتظاهر بأنني رجل لأنني خائف منهم.
Are you messing with me?!
هل أنت تمزح معي؟!
You said I can share problems with you.
قلت أنني أستطيع مشاركة المشاكل معك.
So, you got an operation for that?
إذن، هل أجريت عملية لذلك؟
You had it attached?
هل تم إرفاقه؟
[Denzel chortles]
[يضحك دينزل]
You're so gullible, Jay.
أنت ساذج جدًا، جاي.
- Ouch! That hurts! - I was seriously asking!
- آه! هذا يؤلم! - كنت أسأل بجدية!
You're too pushy. I told you, I'm fine.
أنت متسلط للغاية. لقد أخبرتك أنني بخير.
- I'm just thinking about something. - You were staring into nothing!
- أنا فقط أفكر في شيء ما. - كنت تحدق في لا شيء!
Shut up!
اسكت!
Go argue outside.
اذهب للتجادل خارجا.
Oh, crap.
أوه، يا للأسف.
I thought this was mine?
اعتقدت أن هذا كان لي؟
This is mine now, not yours.
هذه ملكي الآن، وليست ملكك.
Hey, someone sat down with food.
مهلا، جلس شخص ما مع الطعام.
Get out of here.
اخرج من هنا.
There's nothing for us to talk about.
ليس هناك ما نتحدث عنه.
So don't show your face ever again. Get out!
لذا لا تظهر وجهك مرة أخرى أبدًا. اخرج!
Is this really who you are?
هل هذه أنت حقا؟
What?! Canvas Girl #2 is his...
ماذا؟! الفتاة القماشية رقم 2 هي...
Do I have to beg you?
هل يجب علي أن أتوسل إليك؟
Just go!
فقط اذهب!
Someone might see us.
ربما يراني أحد.
Have pity on me.
اشفق علي.
Have pity on us.
ارحمنا.
[Jay-jay gasps]
[يشهق جاي جاي]
Is it really mine?
هل هي حقا ملكي؟
How could you ask me that?!
كيف يمكنك أن تسألني ذلك؟
Just get out of here.
فقط اخرج من هنا.
Don't show yourself here again.
لا تظهر نفسك هنا مرة أخرى. (شاهد على www.kisskh.la أو www.kisskh.co لدعم الإدارة)
Understand?!
يفهم؟!
Denzel!
دنزل!
Jay?
جاي؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Can you please go?!
هل يمكنك الذهاب من فضلك؟
You know we're talking, right?
أنت تعرف أننا نتحدث، أليس كذلك؟
Could you stop screaming at Jay-jay?!
هل يمكنك التوقف عن الصراخ في وجه جاي جاي؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Is it her?
هل هي هي؟
Is she the reason why you won't take responsibility for me?
هل هي السبب في عدم تحملك للمسؤولية عني؟
Hey! No, wait a sec.
مهلا! لا، انتظر لحظة.
It's not because of me.
ليس بسببي .
I don't know anything about that.
لا أعرف شيئا عن هذا.
I just want to talk to Denzel.
أريد فقط التحدث مع دينزل.
Ouch! What's that for?
آآآه! ما هذا؟
You! Why do you talk to women that way?
أنت! لماذا تتحدث مع النساء بهذه الطريقة؟
You both did what you did, and now you're gonna back out?
لقد فعلتما ما فعلتماه، والآن سوف تتراجعان؟
You're gonna leave her hanging?
هل ستتركها معلقة؟
Jay, you wouldn't understand.
جاي، أنت لن تفهم.
Why don't you leave for a bit?
لماذا لا تغادر قليلا؟
Go now. Or I'll hit you again.
اذهب الآن وإلا سأضربك مرة أخرى.
You like meddling, right?
أنت تحب التدخل، أليس كذلك؟
Maybe you can talk to Denzel.
ربما يمكنك التحدث مع دينزل.
Take responsibility for me.
تحمل المسؤولية عني.
The audacity.
الجرأة.
[Canvas Girl #2 cries]
[فتاة القماش رقم 2 تبكي]
Don't order me around.
لا تأمرني بأي شيء.
And stop crying already. The baby might get affected.
وتوقفي عن البكاء الآن، فقد يتأثر الطفل بذلك.
Do your parents know about this?
هل يعلم والداك بهذا الأمر؟
I have no parents.
ليس لدي والدين.
Who did you tell?
من قلت؟
Freya.
فريا.
But she just laughed at me.
لكنها ضحكت مني فقط.
Wow.
رائع.
She said I was an amateur
قالت أنني هاوٍ
that's why I got pregnant.
لهذا السبب حملت.
Great! Such a true friend.
رائع! إنه صديق حقيقي.
[Canvas Girl #2 cries]
[فتاة القماش رقم 2 تبكي]
Stop it now...
اوقفها الآن...
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
Hey, stop crying.
مهلا، توقف عن البكاء.
It's alright. It's gonna be alright.
لا بأس، سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
It's all gonna be fine, Canvas.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام، كانفس.
Canvas?
قماش؟
Grace.
جمال.
- Oh, yeah— - My name is Grace.
- أوه نعم - اسمي جريس.
Stop crying, Grace.
توقفي عن البكاء يا جريس.
I will talk to Denzel.
سأتحدث مع دينزل.
You want me break his bones?
هل تريد مني أن أكسر عظامه؟
Stop crying now. That's enough.
توقف عن البكاء الآن، هذا يكفي.
What is this thing?
ما هذا الشيء؟
Ouch! You're hurting me.
آآآه! أنت تؤذيني.
Your tears. They're massive.
دموعك.. إنها هائلة.
Stop crying now. I'm gonna smash that head of his.
توقف عن البكاء الآن. سأحطم رأسه.
I think I need backup already.
أعتقد أنني بحاجة إلى نسخة احتياطية بالفعل.
It's much better if a mature person will talk to Denzel.
من الأفضل بكثير أن يتحدث شخص ناضج مع دينزل.
Maybe Angelo?
ربما أنجيلو؟
But he'll probably just lecture him. It might put him off.
لكن من المحتمل أن يلقي عليه محاضرة، وقد يؤدي ذلك إلى نفوره.
It could be Ci-N?
هل يمكن أن يكون Ci-N؟
Erase, erase, erase.
امسح، امسح، امسح.
Seems like he could be the one, but no at the same time.
يبدو أنه يمكن أن يكون هو الشخص المناسب، ولكن ليس في نفس الوقت.
A bigger no. He might punch Denzel to death.
لا أكبر. قد يلكم دينزل حتى الموت.
It's gotta be David!
لا بد أن يكون ديفيد!
He's sleeping... but now he's awake.
إنه نائم... لكنه الآن مستيقظ.
[Jay-jay laughs awkwardly]
[يضحك جاي جاي بشكل محرج]
Psst!
هسست!
David.
ديفيد.
Oh?
أوه؟
Let's eat out after class.
دعونا نأكل خارجا بعد انتهاء الفصل الدراسي.
Wow. Jay-jay...
واو. جاي جاي...
are you asking me out on a date?
هل تطلب مني الخروج في موعد؟
Date?!
تاريخ؟!
Date?! Are you two going out?
موعد؟! هل ستخرجان معًا؟
Let me join!
دعني انضم إليك!
Not happening.
لن يحدث.
Why are you only taking David out?
لماذا تأخذ ديفيد فقط للخارج؟
You've changed, Jay.
لقد تغيرت، جاي.
Alright, fine.
حسناً، جيد.
Yes!
نعم!
Then it's settled.
ثم تم تسويتها.
It's a triple date.
إنه تاريخ ثلاثي.
Good thing too. I know a place.
شيء جيد أيضًا، فأنا أعرف مكانًا.
Leave it to me.
اتركها لي.
[Jay-jay and Ci-N happily screaming]
[جاي جاي وسي إن يصرخان بسعادة]
Ouch, Jay. That hurts.
آه، جاي، هذا يؤلمني.
One more time!
مرة أخرى!
- I can't do it anymore! - More!
- لا أستطيع فعل ذلك بعد الآن! - أكثر!
[Ci-N cheering]
[هتاف سي-إن]
The things you do to me.
الأشياء التي تفعلها بي.
Did you enjoy it?
هل استمتعت بها؟
I'm dizzy.
أنا أشعر بالدوار.
Wanna ride one more time?
هل تريد الركوب مرة أخرى؟
I don't want to!
انا لا اريد ذلك!
Sir! Jay-jay said she wants to ride again.
سيدي! قالت جاي جاي إنها تريد الركوب مرة أخرى.
What else do you want? Let's ride one more time.
ماذا تريد أيضًا؟ دعنا نركب مرة أخرى.
Over there.
هناك.
My head's spinning here.
رأسي يدور هنا.
Jay, let's go over there.
جاي، دعنا نذهب إلى هناك.
- One more! One more, Jay! - No more!
- واحدة أخرى! واحدة أخرى، جاي! - لا مزيد!
Come on. Let's ride again.
هيا، دعنا نركب مرة أخرى.
Let's take a break.
دعونا نأخذ استراحة.
You're weak, huh?
أنت ضعيف، أليس كذلك؟
Alright. I'll get some food.
حسنًا، سأحضر بعض الطعام.
Where is David, by the way?
أين ديفيد بالمناسبة؟
Jay!
جاي!
Water?
ماء؟
Here.
هنا.
I said I wanted to talk.
قلت أنني أريد التحدث.
Didn't know that you would bring me to an amusement park.
لم أكن أعلم أنك ستأخذني إلى مدينة الملاهي.
I have extra tickets. Can't let it go to waste.
لدي تذاكر إضافية، ولا يمكنني إهدارها.
Oh.
أوه.
What do you want to talk about?
ماذا تريد أن تتحدث عنه؟
David...
ديفيد...
what if you got your girlfriend pregnant? What will you do?
ماذا لو حملت صديقتك ؟ ماذا ستفعل؟
I'll take full responsibility.
سأتحمل المسؤولية كاملة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل؟
The thing is...
الشيء هو...
Just don't say that you heard it from me.
فقط لا تقل أنك سمعت ذلك مني.
But when you do talk to him, it didn't come from me...
ولكن عندما تتحدث معه، فإن الكلام لم يأتي مني...
How should I put this?
كيف أضع هذا؟
The truth is...
الحقيقة هي...
You know...
أنت تعرف...
It's...
إنه...
It's Denzel.
إنه دينزل.
He doesn't want to take responsibility for Grace.
إنه لا يريد أن يتحمل مسؤولية جريس.
You know already?
هل تعلم بالفعل؟
I heard them fighting.
سمعتهم يتقاتلون.
Oh my goodness. I thought I was the only one who knew.
يا إلهي، كنت أعتقد أنني الوحيد الذي يعرف.
Good thing you know.
شيء جيد أنك تعرف.
I told you. I heard them fighting.
لقد أخبرتك، لقد سمعتهم يتقاتلون.
Can you talk to him? Grace is in a tough spot.
هل يمكنك التحدث معه؟ جريس في موقف صعب.
Denzel has his reasons.
لدى دينزل أسبابه.
He's not that type of person.
إنه ليس من هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
That's why I'm asking you to talk to him.
ولهذا السبب أطلب منك التحدث معه.
Maybe it's better if it's you. 'Cause you're a man.
ربما يكون من الأفضل أن تكون أنت، لأنك رجل.
Alright. I'll talk to him.
حسنًا، سأتحدث معه.
But I can't make any promises that he will change his mind. Okay?
لكن لا يمكنني أن أعده بأنه سيغير رأيه. حسنًا؟
If you can't, maybe Yuri can convince him. Or Keifer.
إذا لم تتمكن من ذلك، فربما يستطيع يوري إقناعه. أو كايفر.
Or anyone that's close to him.
أو أي شخص قريب منه.
Wanna do it now?
هل تريد أن تفعل ذلك الآن؟
Huh?
هاه؟
They're here anyway.
إنهم هنا على أية حال.
Who's they?
من هم؟
Our classmates.
زملاؤنا في الصف.
Really? I don't see them.
حقا؟ أنا لا أراهم.
Want them to come out?
هل تريد منهم أن يخرجوا؟
Close your eyes.
أغمض عينيك.
I know we're in an amusement park. But what is this, magic?
أعلم أننا في مدينة ملاهي، لكن ما هذا، سحر؟
Appear, disappear?
تظهر وتختفي؟
Close your eyes.
أغمض عينيك .698
What's taking so long?
ما الذي يستغرق وقتا طويلا؟
What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟!
Hey.
مرحبا.
Hoy!
اليوم!
Hey! Asshole! Don't you have a girlfriend?!
مهلا! أيها الأحمق! أليس لديك صديقة؟!
Are you insane?
هل انت مجنون؟
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
Maybe.
ربما.
Maybe your face.
ربما وجهك.
This popcorn's really good.
هذا الفشار جيد حقًا.
Hey. You're all here.
مرحبًا، أنتم جميعًا هنا.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
You really prioritized that?
هل أعطيت هذا الأولوية حقًا؟
Why did you leave them unsupervised?
لماذا تركتهم بدون رقابة؟
What are you guys doing here? Are you following us?
ماذا تفعلون هنا؟ هل تتابعوننا؟
You're too much. You asked them on a date without us.
أنت كثير جدًا، لقد طلبت منهم الخروج في موعد بدوننا.
That's right. You know that's so uncool.
هذا صحيح، كما تعلم، هذا ليس بالأمر الرائع.
Should we be side chicks first before we can hang out with you?
هل يجب أن نكون أصدقاء جانبيين أولاً قبل أن نتمكن من الخروج معك؟
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
And to make sure this asshole won't do anything stupid!
وللتأكد من أن هذا الأحمق لن يفعل أي شيء غبي!
What? I didn't do anything.
ماذا؟ لم أفعل شيئا.
You almost kissed her!
لقد كنت على وشك أن تقبلها!
Why are you getting angry?
لماذا تغضب؟
Looks like you're about to shit your pants.
يبدو أنك على وشك التبرز في سروالك.
Get it out. Let's go.
أخرجها، دعنا نذهب.
Let's go. Wanna go to the Horror Hospital?
هيا بنا هل تريد الذهاب إلى مستشفى الرعب؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
[Section E boys chattering]
[القسم E الأولاد يتحدثون]
Hey, Eman!
مرحباً ايمان!
Let's go, Jay.
دعنا نذهب، جاي.
[Keifer clears his throat]
[كيفر يصفي حلقه]
I think it's our turn, guys!
أعتقد أن هذا دورنا يا شباب!
Hey, get out of the way.
مهلا، ابتعد عن الطريق.
I wanna stay with you.
أريد البقاء معك.
Let's ride the Ferris Wheel later, okay?
دعونا نركب عجلة فيريس لاحقًا، حسنًا؟
Boring.
ممل.
Let's go home after this.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل بعد هذا.
Go home if you want. I'm gonna ride it.
اذهب إلى المنزل إذا كنت تريد ذلك، سأركبها.
Right?
يمين؟
[Jay-jay and Ci-N happily dancing]
[جاي جاي وسي إن يرقصان بسعادة]
Wait, wait. Guys. Before we start.
انتظروا، انتظروا يا شباب، قبل أن نبدأ.
What?
ماذا؟
Core memories!
ذكريات جوهرية!
One, two, three.
واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة.
- Yeah! - You're up next.
- نعم! - أنت التالي.
- Oh, it's our turn! - Let's go!
- أوه، لقد حان دورنا! - دعنا نذهب!
- Hey, Ci-N! Take it away. - Yo.
- مهلا، سي-إن! خذها بعيدًا. - يا.
Are you guys ready?
هل أنتم مستعدون؟
We are!
نحن!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
[Section E cheering]
[القسم هـ التشجيع]
Follow me, Jay.
اتبعني يا جاي.
Ci-N's gonna be terrified for sure!
سي-ن سوف يكون مرعوبًا بالتأكيد!
[screaming]
[صراخ]
Are you okay? Are you okay?
هل انت بخير هل انت بخير
- Ouch. - There's someone!
- أوووه. - هناك شخص ما!
[screaming]
[صراخ]
Son of a bitch!
ابن العاهرة!
No touch, no touch!
لا لمس، لا لمس!
You guys come over here. I don't like it here anymore.
تعالوا إلى هنا، لم أعد أحب المكان بعد الآن.
[screaming]
[صراخ]
Wait, wait, wait!
انتظر، انتظر، انتظر!
It's so dark!
إنه مظلم جدًا!
Will you stop doing that? I get scared easily!
هل ستتوقف عن فعل ذلك؟ أنا أخاف بسهولة!
[screaming]
[صراخ]
It's a bridge, guys. We gotta cross.
إنه جسر، يا رفاق، علينا أن نعبره.
[Yuri screams]
[يوري يصرخ]
- It's game on. - Just cross slowly.
- لقد بدأت اللعبة. - فقط اعبر ببطء.
Damn!
اللعنة!
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
- Jay! - [Jay-jay chuckles]
- جاي! - [يضحك جاي جاي]
That's not funny.
هذا ليس مضحكا.
Come on, go inside. Come over here!
هيا، اذهب إلى الداخل، تعال إلى هنا!
Just stay together!
فقط البقاء معا!
- Don't get too rowdy! - Stay close!
- لا تكن صاخبًا جدًا! - ابق قريبًا!
- Ci-N, wait for us! - Slow down, dude!
- سي-إن، انتظرنا! - أبطئ يا صديقي!
- Move quickly! - Game, game, game.
- تحرك بسرعة! - لعبة، لعبة، لعبة.
Wait, let's go together.
انتظر، دعنا نذهب معًا.
Okay.
تمام.
3, 2, 1! Run!
3، 2، 1! اركض!
Run!
يجري!
[screaming]
[صراخ]
[students screaming]
[صراخ الطلاب]
Get out! Out!
اخرجوا! اخرجوا!
- Where is it? - Over there!
- أين هو؟ - هناك!
These morons gets scared too easily.
هؤلاء الحمقى يخافون بسهولة.
- But it's really scary. - Where's Jay-jay?
- لكنه أمر مخيف حقًا. - أين جاي جاي؟
Maybe she went out. Let's wait for her in the end.
ربما خرجت، فلننتظرها في النهاية.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Jay!
جاي!
[Jay-jay panting]
[جاي جاي يلهث]
Ci-N! David! Where are you?!
سي-ن! ديفيد! أين أنت؟!
Ci-N!
ش-ش!
[ghost screeching]
[صراخ الشبح]
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
You're a burden! Useless!
أنت عبء! عديم الفائدة!
You're a worthless child!
أنت طفل لا قيمة لك!
You're gonna get it from me!
سوف تحصل عليه مني!
Please stop it...
من فضلك توقف عن ذلك...
I don't want this...
انا لا اريد هذا...
Jay?!
جاي؟!
[Jay-jay wailing]
[جي جاي يبكي]
Jay! Hey, hey, hey.
جاي! هيا، هيا، هيا.
Hey, hey, hey.
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا.
Hey, hey, hey. I'm here.
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا. أنا هنا.
- [Jay-jay screaming] - I'm here. Are you okay?
- [جاي جاي يصرخ] - أنا هنا، هل أنت بخير؟
Jay!
جاي!
Jay. No. Hey, hey, hey.
جاي. لا. هيا، هيا، هيا.
Hey, Jay!
مهلا، جاي!
- [Jay-jay crying] - It's okay, it's alright. It's just me.
- [جاي جاي يبكي] - لا بأس، لا بأس. الأمر يتعلق بي وحدي.
Jay, breath.
جاي، تنفس.
Breathe.
يتنفس.
- Please, breathe in. - Make it stop...
- من فضلك، تنفس. - اجعله يتوقف...
Breath in, breath out.
تنفس، زفير.
It's okay. It's me. I'm here.
لا بأس، أنا هنا.
I'm here, Jay.
انا هنا، جاي.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
It's gonna be okay. I'm here.
أنا هنا، جاي. كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام. أنا هنا.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Let's get out of here.
دعونا نخرج من هنا.
Okay. Let's go.
حسنا، لنذهب.
- [Jay-jay crying] - It's okay, it's alright. It's just me.
- [جاي جاي يبكي] - لا بأس، لا بأس. الأمر يتعلق بي وحدي.
[Jay-jay crying]
[جاي جاي يبكي]
I wanna go...
أريد أن أذهب...
I'm here. Let's go.
أنا هنا، دعنا نذهب.
[Jay-jay crying]
[جاي جاي يبكي]
Hey, hey, hey.
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا.
Breathe... Please, please. Just breathe.
تنفس... من فضلك، من فضلك. فقط تنفس.
Hey, I'm here.
مهلا، أنا هنا.
I'm here.
انا هنا .848
I won't let go.
لن أتركه.
Okay?
تمام؟
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Yeah?
نعم؟
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
Jay!
جاي!
Jay?!
جاي؟!
Jay?
جاي؟
Keifer!
كيفر!
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Just stay there!
فقط ابقى هناك!
I'll find you, okay?
سأجدك، حسنًا؟
Okay?
تمام؟
I'm scared!
انا خائفة!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Don't be scared!
لا تخف!
Jay, wait for me!
جاي، انتظرني!
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay, alright. Alright... Alright...
حسنًا، حسنًا. حسنًا... حسنًا...
Jay?
جاي؟
Is that you?
هل هذا أنت؟
Mayo. Kit.
يمكن. عدة.
What are you doing here? Where are the others?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟ أين الآخرون؟
We don't know.
نحن لا نعلم.
We're looking for them as well.
نحن نبحث عنهم أيضاً
Wanna look for them together?
هل تريد أن تبحث عنهم معًا؟
Come on.
تعال.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Jay!
جاي!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
I thought I'd never find you.
اعتقدت أنني لن أجدك أبدًا.
Come here, it's okay.
تعال هنا، لا بأس.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Wait.
انتظر.
Are you guys a couple now?
هل أنتم زوجين الآن؟
Are you really?
هل انت حقا؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
No.
رقم
Let's go find the others. Let's go.
دعنا نذهب للبحث عن الآخرين. دعنا نذهب.
Why are you here anyway?
لماذا أنت هنا على أية حال؟
Us? We were lost too.
نحن؟ لقد ضللنا الطريق أيضًا.
Let's just go.
دعنا نذهب فقط.
What happened to you there? You looked stupid!
ماذا حدث لك هناك؟ لقد بدوت غبيًا!
[Section E students happily chattering]
[طلاب القسم E يتحادثون بسعادة]
Hey, there they are!
مهلا، هناك هم!
You're too noisy! I said, they're here already.
أنت مزعج للغاية! قلت، لقد وصلوا بالفعل.
You took too long, dude.
لقد أخذت وقتا طويلا يا صديقي.
My shit's about to come out, I swear.
إن ما بداخلي على وشك أن يخرج، أقسم بذلك.
- Come on, quickly. - Is your poop watery?
- هيا بسرعة. - هل برازك مائي؟
[Ci-N gags]
[نكات سي-إن]
Jay...
جاي...
are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
So, what now?
إذن ماذا الآن؟
Are we still riding the Ferris Wheel or not?
هل مازلنا نركب عجلة فيريس أم لا؟
Ferris Wheel!
عجلة فيريس
Let's ride the Ferris Wheel later, okay?
دعونا نركب عجلة فيريس لاحقًا، حسنًا؟
Boring.
ممل.
Let's go home after this.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل بعد هذا.
Or let's just go home.
أو دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
What?
ماذا؟
I thought you wanted to ride it?
اعتقدت أنك تريد ركوبها؟
Jay, come on. Let's not waste the day.
جاي، هيا، لا تضيعوا اليوم.
We might not get another chance.
ربما لا نحصل على فرصة أخرى.
Alright. Let's go ride the Ferris Wheel.
حسنًا، لنذهب لركوب عجلة فيريس.
[cheering]
[هتاف]
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
I'll wipe my shit on you, guys!
سأمسح قذارتي عليكم يا شباب!
[Jay-jay happily cheering]
[جاي جاي يهتف بسعادة]
Let's go to the Ferris Wheel!
دعونا نذهب إلى عجلة فيريس!
- Come with us already! - There's the Ferris Wheel!
- تعال معنا بالفعل! - هناك عجلة فيريس!
- Just poop later! - Let's go! Ferris Wheel!
- فقط قم بالتبرز لاحقًا! - دعنا نذهب! عجلة فيريس!
My poop's about to come out, dude!
برازي على وشك الخروج، يا صديقي!
[Jay-jay happily cheering]
[جاي جاي يهتف بسعادة]
Oh no.
اوه لا.
The line's too long. Shall we go to another one?
الخط طويل جدًا، هل نذهب إلى مكان آخر؟
No, it's okay.
لا، لا بأس.
We're good here.
نحن بخير هنا.
This ride's dumb. It's only for kids. Like you.
هذه الرحلة غبية، فهي مخصصة للأطفال فقط، مثلك.
Should we go?
هل يجب علينا أن نذهب؟
[Section E boys chattering]
[القسم E الأولاد يتحدثون]
But I want to ride it.
ولكنني أريد ركوبها.
- What if it closes soon? - Don't worry. We"ll be able to ride it.
- ماذا لو أغلقت قريبًا؟ - لا تقلق، سنكون قادرين على ركوبها.
Hey, what's he up to?
مهلا، ماذا يفعل؟
Hi!
أهلاً!
Hi, girls!
مرحباً يا فتيات!
What did he say?
ماذا قال؟
What's he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
Wait, we're listening.
انتظر، نحن نستمع.
I wonder what he’s saying.
أتساءل ماذا يقول؟
He might be using his charm again.
ربما يستخدم سحره مرة أخرى.
Or maybe he’s using his Hanamitchi card again.
أو ربما يستخدم بطاقة هاناميتشي مرة أخرى.
Alright. We'll go ahead.
حسنًا، سنمضي قدمًا.
It worked, dude!
لقد نجحت يا صديقي!
[Section E amazed reaction]
[القسم هـ رد فعل مندهش]
Boys, you know what to do.
يا شباب، أنتم تعرفون ما يجب فعله.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Hello there.
مرحبا بكم.
- Uh, hey guys. - Hi.
- أوه، مرحبًا يا شباب. - مرحبًا.
These assholes...
هؤلاء الحمير...
Yeah, I understand but..
نعم أفهم ذلك ولكن..
It's unfortunate, especially since it's our first date.
إنه أمر مؤسف، خاصة وأن هذا هو موعدنا الأول.
- Are you sure? - Yeah, sure.
- هل أنت متأكد؟ - نعم بالتأكيد.
Keifer already made someone give up their slot.
لقد جعل كايفر شخصًا ما يتخلى عن مكانه بالفعل.
With just a smile, he convinced them.
بمجرد ابتسامة، أقنعهم.
Wow. What great looks he has.
واو، ما أجمل مظهره.
Jay, let's go to the front!
جاي، دعنا نذهب إلى الأمام!
Hey, wait up!
مهلا، انتظر!
Bye!
الوداع!
- Thank you! - Excuse me!
- شكرا لك! - عفواً!
Thank you!
شكرًا لك!
Ci-N!
ش-ش!
Let's go!
هيا بنا!
Here we go!
ها نحن!
Ci-N, CI-N!
ششش، ششش!
This is so amazing. Come on, let's go!
هذا مذهل للغاية. هيا بنا!
I'm so excited, Ci-N!
أنا متحمس جدًا، Ci-N!
Hey, move.
مهلا، تحرك.
There, they're already inside.
هناك، هم بالفعل في الداخل.
Bye!
الوداع!
Hey, where are you going?
مهلا، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
To the Space Shuttle! The one that goes up like that!
إلى المكوك الفضائي! ذلك الذي يصعد إلى الأعلى بهذه الطريقة!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What Space Shuttle?
ما هو المكوك الفضائي؟
How about my...
ماذا عن...؟
Fuck, Drew. That smells horrible.
يا إلهي، درو، هذه الرائحة كريهة للغاية.
Just say if you want to go to the toilet.
فقط قل إذا كنت تريد الذهاب إلى المرحاض.
- Can't you hold it in? - Just go, quickly!
- ألا يمكنك أن تمسك نفسك؟ - فقط اذهب بسرعة!
Just hold it in.
فقط امسكها في داخلك.
It stinks like hell. Good God...
رائحتها كريهة مثل الجحيم. يا إلهي...
[Jay-jay cheers excitedly]
[جاي جاي يهتف بحماس]
Wow!
رائع!
Thank you, Yuri.
شكرا لك يوري.
What did you say to those girls anyway?
ماذا قلت لتلك الفتيات على أية حال؟
I said... I'm gonna confess to the girl I like.
قلت... سأعترف للفتاة التي أحبها.
Huh?
هاه؟
Of course, it was only a joke!
بالطبع، لقد كانت مجرد مزحة!
[Jay-jay chuckles]
[يضحك جاي جاي]
Jay, look at the view! It's so pretty!
جاي، انظر إلى المنظر! إنه جميل جدًا!
Don't move too much!
لا تتحرك كثيرا!
- Jay, look at it! - Hey, stop!
- جاي، انظر إليه! - مهلا، توقف!
I said, keep still!
قلت، ابقى ساكنا!
Ci-N, quit it!
سي-ن، توقف عن هذا!
- Sorry. - Hey, be careful. I don't want to die yet.
- آسف. - هيا، كن حذرًا. لا أريد أن أموت بعد.
Let's take a picture.
دعونا نلتقط صورة.
- Picture? - Yeah.
- صورة؟ - نعم.
- Just look at it, Jay. I swear, you'd like it. - Alright, let me see.
- فقط انظر إليه يا جاي. أقسم أنك ستحبه. - حسنًا، دعني أرى.
All right, guys. I'm taking the photo.
حسنًا يا شباب، سألتقط الصورة.
3, 2, 1. Smile!
3، 2، 1. ابتسم!
One more time.
مرة أخرى.
- Let's do one standing! - Standing?
- لنفعل ذلك واقفا! - واقفا؟ ​​1031
[screams]
[يصرخ]
What happened?!
ماذا حدث؟!
You're being too rowdy! This is your fault!
أنت صاخب للغاية! هذا خطؤك!
Wow. Am I that strong?
واو هل أنا قوية لهذه الدرجة؟
Oh no...
أوه لا...
can't you check what's happening below?
ألا يمكنك التحقق مما يحدث أدناه؟
Now's the time to use your energy.
الآن هو الوقت المناسب لاستخدام طاقتك.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Mechanical failure, Sir.
عطل ميكانيكي يا سيدي.
So, we're stuck here?
إذن نحن عالقون هنا؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Fix it now.
إصلاحه الآن.
Right away, Sir.
في الحال يا سيدي.
Technical issues?
مشاكل فنية؟
Yeah.
نعم.
How long are we gonna be here?
كم من الوقت سوف نبقى هنا؟
Who knows?
من يعلم؟
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
My cellphone! My cellphone!
هاتفي المحمول! هاتفي المحمول!
Hello, Aries.
مرحباً برج الحمل.
Where the hell are you?
أين أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Why aren't you home yet? You're making Angelo worried again.
لماذا لم تعد إلى المنزل بعد؟ أنت تجعل أنجيلو يشعر بالقلق مرة أخرى.
Umm...
اممم...
I'm here at the amusement park.
أنا هنا في مدينة الملاهي.
Great. Where is that?
رائع. أين هذا؟
- Is that the one near our house? - Oh, Jay. That tickles.
- هل هذا هو الذي بالقرب من منزلنا؟ - أوه، جاي. هذا يدغدغ.
Is that Keifer?! Where are you, really?!
هل هذا كايفر؟ أين أنت حقًا؟
- Oh, Jay... - I'm in the Ferris Wheel!
- أوه، جاي... - أنا في عجلة فيريس!
Hey...
يا...
Can you call later?
هل يمكنك الاتصال لاحقا؟
You're disturbing us!
أنت تزعجنا!
[Keifer groans]
[يتأوه كايفر]
Don't stop... Oh, you...
لا تتوقف... أوه، أنت...
- You like it rough? - Give me that!
- هل يعجبك الأمر خشنًا؟ - أعطني هذا!
- Don't stop. - Stop.
- لا تتوقف. - توقف.
Give me my phone.
أعطني هاتفي.
- [Keifer groans] - Give it to me!
- [يئن كيفر] - أعطني إياه!
Answer me.
يجيبني.
- Who's that? - Don't stop... Don't stop...
- من هذا؟ - لا تتوقف... لا تتوقف...
I'll come and get you.
سوف آتي لأخذك.
You're such an asshole.
أنت حقا أحمق.
[Keifer laughing]
[كيفر يضحك]
[Keifer and Ci-N laughing]
[كيفر وسي إن يضحكان]
Was that funny?
هل كان ذلك مضحكا؟
[David laughing]
[ديفيد يضحك]
[boys having fun]
[أولاد يستمتعون]
Stop!
قف!
We need to get unstuck!
نحن بحاجة إلى الخروج من المأزق!
This is the new ride they're building.
هذه هي الرحلة الجديدة التي يبنيونها.
Go get it, Calix, so you can bring it home to Mica.
اذهب واحصل عليه، كاليكس، حتى تتمكن من إحضاره إلى منزل ميكا.
- This one looks like Mykel. - That's your mom, stupid.
- هذا يبدو مثل مايكل. - هذه أمك، أيها الغبي.
See? You didn't shoot anything.
هل رأيت؟ لم تطلق النار على أي شيء.
Party! Party! [cheering]
حفل! حفل! [هتاف]
I'm scared of the Carousel. Mica, I love you.
أنا خائفة من الدوامة. ميكا، أنا أحبك.
- I have a question for you. - Yeah?
- عندي سؤال لك. - نعم؟
Is this how it feels like whenever you spin Mica's head?
هل هذا ما تشعر به عندما تدير رأس ميكا؟
Are you happy about that, huh?
هل أنت سعيد بذلك، أليس كذلك؟
[laughing]
[يضحك]
Giddy up. Giddy up.
متهلل، متهلل.
Wooh!
وو!
Mama!
ماما!
[boys screaming]
[صراخ الأولاد]
You son of a bitch!
يا ابن العاهرة!
My poop's coming out!
برازي يخرج!
So this is how it feels to fall!
لذا هكذا أشعر بالسقوط!
For you.
لك.
[screaming]
[صراخ]
- I wanna get off! - You son of a bitch!
- أريد النزول! - يا ابن العاهرة!
[screaming]
[صراخ]
76, 77...
76, 77...
78...
78...
79...
79...
There's fireworks!
هناك ألعاب نارية!
So cool.
رائع جداً.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Look at it! So pretty.
انظروا إليه! إنه جميل للغاية.
Yeah, so pretty indeed.
نعم، جميلة جدًا بالفعل.
Cliché
كليشيه 1119
What a pretty sight.
ما أجمل هذا المنظر.
So cool!
رائع جداً!
Did you see that?
هل رأيت ذلك؟
Hey. We're moving again.
مهلا، نحن نتحرك مرة أخرى.
Shit!
يا إلهي!
Don't you want to go down?
ألا تريد النزول؟
I wasn't able to take a video of the fireworks!
لم أتمكن من تصوير فيديو للألعاب النارية!
Because of you.
بسببك.
- Give that to me! - Uh-uh.
- أعطني هذا! - اه اه.
- Give it to me. - No.
- أعطني إياه. - لا.
I told you to give it back!
لقد قلت لك أن تعيدها!
What if I fall off?
ماذا لو سقطت؟
Now you're scared of falling.
الآن أنت خائف من السقوط.
Last time, you jumped, right?
في المرة الأخيرة، قفزت، أليس كذلك؟
Hello? This is too high. I could die.
مرحبًا؟ هذا مرتفع جدًا، قد أموت.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll catch you again if you fall.
سأمسكك مرة أخرى إذا سقطت.
So cliché.
كليشيه جداً.
- Give it to me. - No.
- أعطني إياه. - لا.
I'm getting really pissed. I said, give it back.
لقد شعرت بالغضب الشديد، فقلت له: أعيدها.
- Give it here! - No.
- أعطها هنا! - لا.
Give it to me!
أعطيني إياها!
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
[Ci-N laughs]
[يضحك سي-إن]
See?
يرى؟
I told you I'll still catch you.
لقد قلت لك أنني سأمسك بك.
Get off.
ترجل.
Stop.
قف.
Yuri, will you help me?
يوري هل ستساعدني؟
This guy...
هذا الرجل...
Keifer!
كيفر!
- Jay... - Don't! Don't!
- جاي... - لا تفعل! لا تفعل!
Don't!
لا!
- Help me. - Do not.
- ساعدني. - لا تفعل.
- Don't. - Please.
- من فضلك.
Don't!
لا!
[Jay-jay grunts]
[جاي جاي يئن]
What the hell is wrong with you?!
ماذا حدث لك بحق الجحيم؟!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
[screaming]
[صراخ]
[Ci-N laughs]
[يضحك سي-إن]
Ouch! You're so heavy!
آآآه! أنت ثقيل جدًا!
What the hell?!
بحق الجحيم؟!
Ouch, Yuri. I said help me!
آه، يوري. قلت ساعدني!
What's with the face?
ما الأمر مع الوجه؟
Ouch! My feet, Jay!
آخ! قدمي، جاي!
Why are you laughing?! Come and help me!
لماذا تضحك؟ تعال وساعدني!
What the...
ماذا...
Ouch...
آخ...
Jasper Jean Mariano!
جاسبر جان ماريانو!
Get off!
ترجل!
It's your fault!
إنه خطؤك!
I'll tell Angelo to ground you!
سأطلب من أنجيلو أن يبقيك على الأرض!
Hey! I'm still talking to you. Where are you going?
مهلا! مازلت أتحدث إليك. إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Upstairs!
الطابق العلوي!
Stop hanging out with that Keifer!
توقف عن التسكع مع هذا كايفر!
He'll just pull you down with him!
سوف يسحبك إلى الأسفل معه!
It was just a coincidence. I was really with Ci-N and David.
لقد كانت مجرد مصادفة. كنت في الحقيقة مع سي إن وديفيد.
No matter who it is, you're not gonna hang out with anyone from Section E.
بغض النظر عن من هو، فلن تتمكن من التسكع مع أي شخص من القسم E.
You too much. You're acting stricter than Angelo.
أنت أكثر من اللازم. أنت تتصرف بشكل أكثر صرامة من أنجيلو.
I'll tell on you.
سأخبرك.
I said I'm sorry.
قلت أنني آسف.
Maybe you already have feelings for that Keifer.
ربما لديك بالفعل مشاعر تجاه كايفر.
I won't let go.
لن أتركه.
Jay!
جاي!
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
I told you I'll still catch you.
لقد قلت لك أنني سأمسك بك.
Why can't you answer?
لماذا لا تستطيع الرد؟
Did you really catch feelings for Keifer?
هل حقا شعرت بمشاعر تجاه كايفر؟
Are you crazy? I don't even like him!
هل انت مجنون؟ انا لا احبه حتى!
Jay-jay!
جاي جاي!
I didn't expect that Denzel would be living in a place like this.
لم أتوقع أن دينزل سيعيش في مكان كهذا.
David!
ديفيد!
Thanks for taking me here.
شكرا على اصطحابي إلى هنا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I already told the others, so we can come up with a solution to Denzel's problem.
لقد أخبرت الآخرين بالفعل، حتى نتمكن من التوصل إلى حل لمشكلة دينزل.
I just don't know if they can make it this early.
أنا لا أعرف إذا كان بإمكانهم القيام بذلك في وقت مبكر.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
- Oh. It's you. - Is Denzel here?
- أوه، إنه أنت. - هل دينزل هنا؟
He's inside.
إنه في الداخل.
Wait, I'll just call him.
انتظر، سأتصل به.
Thank you.
شكرا لك .1211
Denzel, someone's looking for you.
دينزل، هناك شخص يبحث عنك.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Jay-jay needs to talk to you.
جاي جاي يحتاج إلى التحدث معك.
Go. Talk to him.
اذهب وتحدث معه.
[Jay-jay smiles awkwardly]
[يبتسم جاي جاي بشكل محرج]
I understand if you would judge me after hearing the truth.
أفهم إذا كنت ستحكم علي بعد سماع الحقيقة.
I just used Grace.
لقد استخدمت جريس فقط.
You see our place, right?
هل ترى مكاننا، أليس كذلك؟
How did you use her?
كيف استخدمتها؟
My mom works at their house.
أمي تعمل في منزلهم.
She lives with her aunt and they're rich.
تعيش مع عمتها وهم أغنياء.
I'm envious of rich people, that's why...
أنا أحسد الأغنياء، لهذا السبب...
I told myself I'll do anything to be like them.
قلت لنفسي سأفعل أي شيء لأكون مثلهم.
And you used Grace as a tool?
واستخدمت النعمة كأداة؟
I befriended her.
لقد أصبحت صديقا لها.
I tried being playful with her, even though she was always snarky towards me.
لقد حاولت أن أكون مرحًا معها، على الرغم من أنها كانت دائمًا ساخرة تجاهي.
Until she got comfortable with me.
حتى أصبحت مرتاحة معي.
I tricked her into getting me enrolled at HVIS.
لقد خدعتها لتسجيلي في HVIS.
When I got into the school,
عندما دخلت المدرسة،
I started ignoring Grace.
بدأت بتجاهل جريس.
I felt guilty.
لقد شعرت بالذنب.
She kept talking to me.
لقد استمرت بالتحدث معي.
Kept giving me nice things.
استمر بإعطائي أشياء لطيفة.
Cellphone. Shoes.
الهاتف المحمول.الأحذية.
I thought she'll get tired of me that's why I just let her be.
اعتقدت أنها سوف تمل مني ولهذا السبب تركتها وشأنها.
I'm reaping all the benefits after all.
أنا أحصد كل الفوائد بعد كل شيء.
We became a couple, but kept it secret.
لقد أصبحنا زوجين، لكننا أبقينا الأمر سراً.
I tried breaking up with her but...
لقد حاولت الانفصال عنها ولكن...
I can't do it.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
Because...
لأن...
Because you finally loved her?
لأنك أحببتها أخيرا؟
I'm afraid of losing her.
أنا خائف من فقدانها.
She won't forgive me once she finds out the truth.
لن تسامحني عندما تكتشف الحقيقة.
I will do anything to take responsibility, but...
سأفعل أي شيء لتحمل المسؤولية، ولكن...
But Grace?
ولكن النعمة؟
Grace?
نعمة؟
I understand Grace's feelings.
أنا أفهم مشاعر جريس.
It hurts so much more when the words...
يؤلمني كثيرًا عندما تكون الكلمات...
are uttered by the person you love.
تنطق بها من تحب.
You're a liar.
أنت كاذب.
Grace!
جمال!
- Grace!
- نعمة!
Please, let's talk about this!
من فضلك، دعونا نتحدث عن هذا!
Don't come near me!
لا تقترب مني!
I will jump if you come near me.
سأقفز إذا اقتربت مني.
I know you're used to hurting others.
أعرف أنك معتاد على إيذاء الآخرين.
But even the ones you love, you wanna hurt?
ولكن حتى من تحبهم، هل تريد أن تؤذيهم؟
They killed him, Jay. He died!
لقد قتلوه، جاي. لقد مات!
All of you wants to save Grace!
أنتم جميعا تريدون إنقاذ جريس!
But how about my brother? Huh?
ولكن ماذا عن أخي؟ هاه؟
No one dared to save him!
لم يجرؤ أحد على انقاذه!
You really went out of your way to come here, huh?
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك لتأتي إلى هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Talk to me. Okay, you're mad at Aries.
تحدث معي. حسنًا، أنت غاضب من برج الحمل.
But why do you have to get mad at me too?
ولكن لماذا عليك أن تغضب مني أيضًا؟
Could you stop meddling in other people's lives?
هل بإمكانك التوقف عن التدخل في حياة الآخرين؟
Keifer! Keifer!
كيفر! كيفر!
What the hell are you shouting about?
ما الذي تصرخ به بحق الجحيم؟
- It's Jay-jay! - What happened to Jay-jay?
- إنه جاي جاي! - ماذا حدث لجاي جاي؟
It's Ram. I didn't see them, but I'm sure!
إنه رام. لم أرهم، ولكنني متأكد!
Jay!
جاي!
Hi, boys!
مرحباً يا شباب!
What? Missed me?
ماذا؟ هل افتقدتني؟
Where is Jay-jay?!
أين جاي جاي؟!
Ram called Kiko!
رام يسمى كيكو!
I'm sure she got caught up in your troubles again!
أنا متأكد من أنها وقعت في مشاكلك مرة أخرى!
I'm gonna fuck them up if they touch her! I swear!
سأقوم بإفسادهم إذا لمسوها! أقسم بذلك!
Wait, let me ask you first.
انتظر، دعني أسألك أولاً.
Do you like Jay-jay?
هل تحب جاي جاي؟
I think I'm falling for her.
أعتقد أنني أقع في حبها.